<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pratik Gajjar on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Pratik Gajjar on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learnings</title><link>/learning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/learning/</guid><description/></item><item><title>👋 Let’s connect</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>We can discuss about Career Guidance, Web Optimisation, Working in FinTech or Startup, Dev Ops, Resume Review, Django etc . .</description></item><item><title>📝 Resume</title><link>/resume/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/resume/</guid><description>EXPERIENCE Engineering Team
Employer: FamPay.in | Apr, 20 - Current | Bengaluru
TODO Senior Software Engineer
Employer: Truebil.com | Nov, 19 - Apr, 20 | Mumbai
Optimized and developed new APIs of Truebil’s Progressive Web App which is now part of Google Case Study. Achieved Avg response time of 51ms from 180ms. Resulting 80% increase in revenue-to-marketing spend. (Django-REST-Framework, Mysql 5.7, Redis)Ref: How Truebil made the web its channel of growth Architect redis caching layer of backend api, which resulted in +435% throughput capacity and 66% reduction of EC2 instance consumption.</description></item><item><title>🧙 About Me</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>As of Apr 2021 As a backend engineer at FamPay, he finds joy in tackling various engineering challenges and even some non-engineering problems. His passion lies in problem-solving, regardless of the nature of the task at hand.
A Typical Day In My Work Life My workday usually starts by going through emails and checking Slack messages where I&amp;rsquo;ve been tagged. I make sure to stay up-to-date with any important communications and address engineering-related issues in public threads, offering my assistance whenever possible.</description></item><item><title>🕵️‍♂️ Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:23:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The following information is collected:</description></item></channel></rss>