<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pratik Gajjar on</title><link>https://pratikgajjar.in/contributors/pratik-gajjar/</link><description>Recent content in Pratik Gajjar on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pratikgajjar.in/contributors/pratik-gajjar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>👋 Let’s connect</title><link>https://pratikgajjar.in/contact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pratikgajjar.in/contact/</guid><description>We can discuss about Carrier Guidance, Web Optimisation, Working in FinTech or Startup, Dev Ops, Resume Review, Django etc . .
Why: I am doing this? It’s an inexplicable feeling: someone who can guide you, who has been through the exact same phase as you are going through, someone who has a subject matter expertise, someone who can provide a different perspective, or someone who has connections in the area you are looking to break through.</description></item><item><title>📝 Resume</title><link>https://pratikgajjar.in/resume/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pratikgajjar.in/resume/</guid><description>EXPERIENCE Engineering Team
Employer: FamPay.in | Apr, 20 - Current | Bengaluru
TODO Senior Software Engineer
Employer: Truebil.com | Nov, 19 - Apr, 20 | Mumbai
Optimized and developed new APIs of Truebil’s Progressive Web App which is now part of Google Case Study. Achieved Avg response time of 51ms from 180ms. Resulting 80% increase in revenue-to-marketing spend. (Django-REST-Framework, Mysql 5.7, Redis)Ref: How Truebil made the web its channel of growth Architect redis caching layer of backend api, which resulted in +435% throughput capacity and 66% reduction of EC2 instance consumption.</description></item><item><title>🧙 About Me</title><link>https://pratikgajjar.in/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pratikgajjar.in/about/</guid><description>As of Apr 2021 I&amp;rsquo;ve been working at FamPay as a backend engineer.
A Typical Day In My Work Life Solving problems at FamPay be it infra or new features. Learning advance database features and dev ops stuff Hiring &amp;amp; Reviews</description></item><item><title>🕵️‍♂️ Privacy Policy</title><link>https://pratikgajjar.in/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:23:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://pratikgajjar.in/privacy-policy/</guid><description>TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The following information is collected:</description></item></channel></rss>